sanyglobal.com 2019-06-15

# Privacy Policy | SANY Privacy | Excavator Manufacturers - SANY Group

Privacy Policy

This privacy statement is being provided to you to explain what information [SANY Group](http://www.sanyglobal.com/company-profile.html) is collecting from you through your use of this website (Hereinafter referred to as “Site”) and how it uses this information.

Personal Information

Generally, you can browse this Site without providing your name and other personal information. Some times, the Site may need your personal information. For example, we need your e-mail address, name, contact information when you email us or register for free subscription; we need your name, gender, age and education experience when you apply for a job on our website. We may need such information to fulfill a transaction or provide better service.

When you visit this Site, it automatically collects certain information about you and your request (e.g., your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, the content that you request), and other information provided by your browser (e.g. browser name, referral site). This information may be used to improve the content and usefulness of this Site, to understand your usage of the Site and to customize content based on your usage. We don’t connect this information with your personal data.

Cookies

When you visit this Site we will send you a cookie. A cookie stores a small data file on your computer. This file enables us to recognize you each time you visit us. Cookies help us in many ways, for example, by saving your region and language preference and for purposes of collecting non-personal data.

If you do not allow this website to use cookies, then certain features or sections of the Site may not be available to you or may not function as expected. Cookies can also be removed or blocked by following the help directions in your browser.

Security

[SANY Group](http://www.sanyglobal.com/company-profile.html) utilizes reasonable security measures designed to secure your information. Servers where personal information is stored are password and firewall-protected, and access is limited to those employees and independent contractors with a need to know and only for the purposes identified above. We maintain safeguards intended to protect the security, integrity, and privacy of these servers and of your personal information.

Third party links

There may be third party web sites that you may link to from this Web Site. For example, we allow you to link to Facebook, Twitter and various other social media sites from this Web Site. However, SANY Group has no control over these linked web sites and they each have separate privacy and data collection practices, independent of SANY Group. These third party web sites may track your browsing activity across this Web Site as well as across other sites you visit. [SANY Group](http://www.sanyglobal.com/company-profile.html) has no responsibility or liability for these independent policies or actions and is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites. These linked web sites are only for your convenience and you therefore access them at your own risk.

Disclaimer

In the following cases, this website does not undertake any responsibility.

1\. We disclose information to law enforcement, governmental agencies, or third-parties authorized by law, in response to a verified request relating to a criminal investigation or alleged illegal activity or any other activity that may expose us, you, or any other Web Site user to legal liability. In such events, we will disclose information that we believe to be relevant and necessary to the investigation or inquiry.

2\. Any personal data disclosure caused by sharing registered accounts with others or informing others of your password or caused by other personal reasons.

3\. Any personal data is disclosed, lost, stolen and manipulated by computer virus or by network temporary shutdown caused by irresistible factors.

4\. Personal data is disclosed by other websites linked to this Web Site and any legal dispute and consequence arising therefrom.

5\. Other cases leading to personal data disclosure by our unintentional faults.

Applicable Laws

Any controversy or lawsuit arising out of or relating to this privacy policy shall be settled by the law of the People's Republic of China.

[SANY Group](http://www.sanyglobal.com/company-profile.html) has the right to explain, revise and update the privacy policy.
